meetyourmessenger.co.uk 2008-09-14

# MeetYourMessenger.co.uk

**Art. 1 – About.**

(1)   This privacy statement is incorporated into and subject to “MeetYourMessenger’s terms of use.” MeetYourMessenger is dedicated to online privacy, so in case you have any questions concerning this privacy statement, please contact us at our support center: [http://www.MeetYourMessenger.co.uk/faq.aspx](http://www.meetyourmessenger.co.uk/faq.aspx)

(2)   MeetYourMessenger is a virtual map of Messenger users. We connect you to anyone who is connected to MeetYourMessenger and you will be able to track back how you know these people in real life. MeetYourMessenger makes it possible for you to seek and find other Messenger users in your country, in your area or even in your city. You can see their picture, see who they are, see who their friends are, ask them what they work with, what their education is and much more.

**Art. 2 – Information collected by MeetYourMessenger.**

(1)     **User Provided Information:** You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to MeetYourMessenger when choosing to participate in various activities on MeetYourMessenger such as uploading pictures, posting articles in The MYM Times, answering questions, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. MeetYourMessenger collects such user submitted information (e.g. name, email address, and age) to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the MeetYourMessenger service. MeetYourMessenger also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

(2)     **Cookies Information:** When you visit MeetYourMessenger, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. MeetYourMessenger uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the MeetYourMessenger may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

(3)     **Log File Information:** When you use the MeetYourMessenger Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

(4)     **Clear GIFs Information:** When you use MeetYourMessenger, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

**Art. 3 – Use of information.**

(1)     User Profile information including members´ pictures and profile name are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the MeetYourMessenger social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join MeetYourMessenger, to add users to members´ friends´ networks, and to send notifications related to the service. When importing Messenger contact information, a personal invitation-email is sent to the contacts, which has been imported. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user´s email address is not shared or displayed to other users, except when the user consents to this. Users communicate on MeetYourMessenger with each other through the MeetYourMessenger service, without disclosing their email addresses. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, MeetYourMessenger allows users to search for other members using name, postal code, gender and age.

(2)     We may also use a user´s email address and profile information to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. These emails may contain advertisement and marketing messages for third parties. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by going to “My Profile" and setting the "Do not send me notification emails" function.

(3)     We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of MeetYourMessenger and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. The information may also be used to personalize your profile and the information that you are given, while using MeetYourMessenger.

(4)     We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to the following purposes: 

·        Remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the MeetYourMessenger.

·        Provide custom, personalized content and information

·        Monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns

·        Monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and 

·        Track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

## Art. 4 - Disclosing information.

(1)     We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy statement, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

(2)     MeetYourMessenger may transfer information to other corporate entities, that are wholly owned by MeetYourMessenger or a part of the Meet group or Shared group.

(3)     We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

(4)     We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on MeetYourMessenger. 

(5)     We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with the laws of a country (such as UK or German Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

(6)     MeetYourMessenger also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that MeetYourMessenger believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MeetYourMessenger, our Users or others.

**Art. 5. – Emails.**

So which emails can you expect to get from us?

(1)   Types of E-mails

§         Invitation emails

§         User initiated emails

§         Newsletters

§         Updates

§         Surveys

§         Special offers

(2)   Emails will always be sent from a meetyourmessenger domain and will come from either MeetYourMessenger itself or an entity from the Meet group or Shared group.

**Art. 6. – Where is the information kept?**

The MeetYourMessenger sites are hosted in Denmark and the information collected on the MeetYourMessenger websites are kept on the MeetYourMessenger servers, which are placed in Copenhagen, Denmark. Users of the MeetYourMessenger websites accept that the collected information is stored on these servers, thereby transferred across any boarders between their residing country and Denmark. Please be advised that through your continued use of MeetYourMessenger, which are governed by Danish law, this Privacy Statement and our Terms, you are transferring your personal information to Denmark and you consent to that transfer.

##  

## Art. 6. - User rights.

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the MeetYourMessenger websites, in which case MeetYourMessenger may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your “My profile” page.  Please note that Questions and Answers, Articles and Messenger connections uploaded by Users to the MeetYourMessenger websites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

Opt-Out and information:  
With regard to personal information that you have provided under this Privacy Policy, there are several opt-out choices available to you. These opt-out choices are the means by which you give us, or decline to give us, your consent to use your personal information for the purposes covered by these opt-out choices.

Your choices are:

Option 1: You may choose to opt out of receiving promotional materials from third parties. MeetYourMessenger may not share nonpublic personal information with nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. If you do not choose this opt-out, MeetYourMessenger may share your personal information so that third parties can send you promotional materials.

Option 2: You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from any of the Meet group or Shared group companies, including MeetYourMessenger. MeetYourMessenger may not share certain nonpublic personal information among its affiliates, except as permitted by law. In doing so, You may choose to opt out of all promotional materials from all entities or specify which types of material You would like to accept and from whom. This can be done partly under “my profile” on the MeetYourMessenger webpage.

Option 3: You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from all of the Meet group and Shared group companies and third parties.

Option 4: You have the right at all times to obtain the information saved by MeetYourMessenger.

NOTE: None of these opt-out choices applies in the following situations:  
a) You at a later time specifically accept or request for information from MeetYourMessenger.  
b) The information is being used by MeetYourMessenger for either operational or fulfillment purposes.  
c) If required by Law.  
d) If required to help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Web Site

Request regarding opt-out options must be addressed to:

MeetYourMessenger A/S  
Att.: Privacy Statement  
Postboks 68  
7100  Vejle  
Denmark

Requests must be written, contain your email and a copy of your driver’s license or other ID including a picture and information that confirms your address. 

Please also feel free to contact MeetYourMessenger with any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using our support center.

**Art. 7 - Security.**

MeetYourMessenger member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. MeetYourMessenger takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. MeetYourMessenger uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to MeetYourMessenger and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, MeetYourMessenger makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If MeetYourMessenger learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. MeetYourMessenger may post a notice on MeetYourMessenger if a security breach occurs. 

**Art. 8 - Changes to this privacy statement.**

This Privacy Statement may be revised from time to time. This will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Statement in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of MeetYourMessenger constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any future revisions. If, however, we are going to use users´ personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice to your email address.

**Art. 9. Acceptance.**

The users of the MeetYourMessenger websites acknowledge their acceptance to this privacy statement by visiting one of the MeetYourMessenger websites. 

This Privacy Statement is effective as of the 24th January 2008.
